The greatest artist you've never heard of.
Struggle: The Life and Lost Art of Szukalski is a
documentary film directed by Irek Dobrowolski.
Artists in LA discover the work of forgotten Polish sculptor Stanislav Szukalski, a
mad genius whose true story unfolds chapter by astounding chapter.
Self (archive footage), played by Stanisław Szukalski.
Self - Collector, played by Glenn Bray.
Self - Painter and Illustrator, played by Robert Williams.
Self - Artist, played by Suzanne Williams.
Self - Artist, Writer, Distributor, played by George DiCaprio.
Self - Painter (archive footage), played by Ernst Fuchs.
Struggle: The Life and Lost Art of Szukalski is a 2018 documentary film directed by Irek Dobrowolski, written by
Stephen Cooper and Irek Dobrowolski and starring Stanisław Szukalski, Glenn Bray and Robert Williams.
The documentary is produced by Leonardo DiCaprio,
and his father George DiCaprio.
The film was released by Netflix on December 21, 2018.